wjfw.com 2019-12-12

# WJFW TV-12, WJFWDT 12.1 and Newswatch 12 - Your Northwoods News Leader and NBC Affiliate - Rhinelander Wisconsin

## PRIVACY POLICY

**WJFW-TV (Northland Television, Inc.)** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.wjfw.com This privacy policy applies only to information collected by or through this Web site. It does not apply to information obtained by other means.

**Information Collection and Use**  
We collect information from Web site visitors who must register for certain services on-line, from users who agree to participate in on-line surveys, from users who wish to make certain online information requests from us and from users who wish to participate in on-line contests and promotions sponsored by us. Because participation in these activities is completely voluntary, the user has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The type of information so requested or collected by us includes user contact information (like their name and email address) and user demographic information (like gender or age). Contact information will be used to notify contest winners and award prizes and, in some instances may be shared with the contest or survey sponsor. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of reporting survey results and monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. The visitor's contact information will be used to contact the visitor when the visitor has expressed interest in being contacted (visitors can opt-out of receiving future mailings by complying with the choice/output requirements noted below).

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We track and record IP addresses that access our site for reporting and profiling purposes only. We may also share personally identifiable user information if requested to do so by subpoena or with governmental authorities when subpoenaed to do so or as part of an investigation into illegal activities, such as, but not limited to illegal transfer of copyrighted material, or user Web site postings or email messages that contain threats of violence. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in other cases where we have reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use. Other than these specific exceptions noted, we do not sell, rent or provide access to any data collected about or from our users.

**Aggregate Information/Use of Cookies**  
On the Internet, a �cookie� is a piece of information (a file) that a website transfers to a user�s computer for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common on the Internet. The process we use to serve advertisements and to track use of the Site involves cookies. We use cookies to recognize users who have already registered on our Site, allowing those users to speed up their future activities on the Site. Cookies help Operator track the frequency and placement of products and services on the Site. Cookies also enable us to measure aggregate (total) usage and traffic to the Site and to specific offerings. This aids us in producing content that best meets our users� preferences. In order to implement new products or services, we may use other types of cookies as well. We also may use cookies to understand better what parts of the Site you like best. We may use that information to display advertisements and provide services and products that we think will be of particular interest to you. You may configure your browser to reject cookies, but this may interfere with some functionality of the Site.

**Linking and Framing**  
WJFW.com contains links to other sites. WJFW is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Occasionally when linking to another site, you may still see our site's logo or frame. This is to provide you with a seamless experience when visiting our Web site. In these cases you are no longer on WJFW.COM and are now on a different Web site whose information collection practices may differ from ours. The privacy policy of the site you are on will govern how information collected from you is used.

**Security**  
This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please remember that no computer system should be considered safe from intrusion. Email may pass through many computer systems, and should not be considered as a secure means of communication unless encrypted. Even then, information is only as secure as the encryption method. Access is limited to a very small number of employees with a defined need and is password protected. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. You will notice in emails generated from this Web site there is an unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message. Simply click on this link to go to a page that allows you to unsubscribe from any or all of the lists you are subscribed to.  
In addition to using the unsubscribe page, you can send an email to webmaster@wjfw.com.

**Contacting the Web site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

**Web Site Administrator  
WJFW-TV  
3217 County Rd. G  
Rhinelander, WI 54501  
webmaster@wjfw.com**
